-Phoebe,could you get that,please? -Why?
菲比，可以麻烦接个电话吗？ 为什么？
Just because you're too lazy to get up off your tushy?
就因为你懒得动？
No,it's just that all the people in the world I would want to talk to are right here.
不是，只是因为在全世界 我只想跟你说话
好吧
Sucker.
真好骗
Hello?
喂？
-Hey,Joey! -Hey,Phoebe.
乔伊 菲比
I need a favor.
帮我个忙好吗？
I forgot the PlN to my ATM card. Can you get it for me?
我忘记提款卡的密码 你可以帮我去找吗？
Sure. Where is it?
好啊，在哪里？
I scratched it on the ATM machine on the corner.
我刻在提款机的角落那里
So you're 5-6-3-9?
原来5639是你的密码
That's it! Thanks.
没错，菲比，谢了
-Wanna talk to Chandler? -Let me talk to him.
你要跟钱德说话吗？ 是乔伊吗？让我跟他说
He didn't believe in my movie...
不要！他不相信我的电影
...which is a big mistake, because it is real. Real.
他大错特错 这次的电影是真的！…
Tribbiani,get back to work. Break time's over.
崔比亚尼 快回去工作，休息时间结束了
-Who was that? -My stunt double. Yeah.
刚才那个是谁？ 我的替身
He's getting a little too familiar for my tastes.
他有点太没大没小了
I've tried to apologize.
我这星期来都试着跟他道歉
If I can't do it on the phone, I'll go and do it in person.
若他不让我在电话上说 我就直接杀过去当面说
I heard that. Can you put him on?
菲比，我听到了，请他听电话
好
Don't come out here.
你别过来
I support you 100% and I wanna prove that to you in person.
不行…我百分之百支持你 我要当面证明给你看
I got that. I forgive you. Don't come out here.
收到，我原谅你，你别过来
You haven't taken my calls for a week.
原谅我？ 你一星期都不接我电话
I'm totally over it. Friends forever. Don't come out here.
钱德，我早都不介意了 咱们是一辈子的朋友 你别过来
Would you mind doing a picture with us?
可以跟我们照张相吗？
-What was that? -Entertainment Tonight.
那是什么？ “今夜娱乐”节目
Good talking to you and don't come out here.
好了，很高兴跟你说话 你别过来
The One in Vegas
本集播出：“赌城行”
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
Monica? I'm sorry I'm late.
摩妮卡，抱歉我迟到了
摩妮卡？
菲比？
I'm so sorry. Have you been here long?
菲比，真对不起 你到很久了吗？
That's okay.
没关系啦
What the hell took you so long?
你怎么拖了那么久？
You can't tell Chandler. I ran into Richard.
好，不许你跟钱德说 我遇见了理查
-Which Richard? -The Richard.
哪个理查？ 那个理查
Richard Simmons? Oh,my God!
理查西蒙斯?（减重专家） 天啊
No,my ex-boyfriend Richard. You know, the tall guy, mustache.
不是啦，是我前男友理查 个子高高，有胡子那个
Okay, that actually makes more sense. How was it?
好吧，这就说得过去了 情况如何？
It was really nice. We talked and I had lunch with him.
好极了，我们先是闲聊 后来一起吃了个午饭
That's weird. I dreamed you had lunch with Richard.
怪了，我有梦到你跟理查吃饭
-Really? -Again, Richard Simmons.
真的？ 不过是跟理查西蒙斯啦
Go on.
你继续说
The strange part was he was really nice...
奇怪的是虽然他很棒也很帅
...and he looks great, but I didn't feel anything.
但是我对他完全没感觉了
So why can't we tell Chandler?
那为什么不能跟钱德说？
It'll freak him out and tomorrow's our anniversary. I don't wanna spoil it.
因为他听了一定会发神经 明天就是我们的纪念日 我不想搞砸
I can't believe you guys have lasted a whole year!
不敢相信你们交往一年了
Wow, I owe Rachel 20 bucks.
我欠瑞秋20美元
On a totally different bet.
那是完全不相干的赌局啦
-It's almost our anniversary! -I know.
一周年纪念日快到了 我知道
One year ago today,I was just your annoying friend Chandler.
你相信吗？一年前的今天 我还是只是烦人的朋友钱德
Now you're just my annoying friend Chandler.
现在你是我烦人的朋友钱德
I got you a gift.
我帮你买了礼物
-It's not till tomorrow. -I know,but you have to open it today.
纪念日明天才到 我知道，但你今天就要开礼物
Okay! There you go!
我来啦
It's two tickets to Vegas!
两张去赌城的机票
Yeah! For this weekend! It'll be perfect.
这周末的来回机票 一定很完美
You'll see Joey, plus,we'll start our celebration on the plane.
不但能去看乔伊 还能在飞机上开始过纪念日
We can call it our "Plane-aversary."
就叫做“飞机纪念日”吧
Do we have to?
一定要这样叫？
This is great, but Joey didn't want any of us there.
这是很棒没错 但乔伊说了不要我们过去
He doesn't want us to go to any trouble. He'll be excited when we surprise him.
他只是怕麻烦我们而已 到时我们突然出现 他一定超兴奋的
Plus,we get to have our own "Anna-Vegas-ry"!
而且我们自己还有赌城纪念日
"Anna-vada-versary!"
内华达纪念日！
I think we should see other people.
对，我们该开始和别人交往
We can go, right?
我们可以去吧？ 对
Great idea.
那就好 这是个好主意
I'm gonna go too!
好耶，我也要去
Phoebe,it's kind of our anniversary.
菲比，这是我俩的纪念日耶
You won't ditch me like you did with London.
少来，休想比照伦敦那次 把我甩掉
Ditch you? You were pregnant
菲比，哪有甩掉？ 当时你怀了三胞胎耶
Great story. I'm going.
真会掰，我非去不可
Listen, this weekend we're all gonna go to Las Vegas to surprise Joey!
注意，这周末大家一起去赌城 给乔伊一个惊喜
Including me!
包括我！
Do you wanna go?
你们要去吗？
I can take a couple days off work.
我应该可以请个几天假
Of course you can take a couple days off, because this trip includes me!
你当然可以请几天假 因为这趟我也要去！
I've got a presentation tomorrow. I can't miss that.
等等，差点忘了 我明天要提报告，不能缺席
I've got tickets to the Van Gogh exhibit. I waited a year for this.
我也买了梵谷画展的票 我盼了一年才盼到
Art lover.
艺术爱好者
What'd you say?
你说什么？
I said,art lover.
我说艺术爱好者
-Was that supposed to be an insult? -I don't know,I'm very tired.
那是用来侮辱人的吗？ 不知道，我很累了
-Rach, maybe we can fly out Saturday? -Sounds great.
瑞秋，不如你我周六再飞去？ 听起来很可行
I'll call the airlines.
好，那我打电话去订票
That'll be nice to have the apartment to myself.
其实想起来很不赖 我可以独自在公寓过一晚
To walk around naked.
对，你可以脱光光到处走
No,so I can be by myself. Have a little alone time.
不是，我可以自己一个人 享受独处的时光
Naked alone time.
脱光光的独处时光
Just because I'm alone doesn't mean I wanna walk around naked.
菲比，我一个人独处 并不表示我就想脱光光到处走
You live alone, you don't walk around naked.
你自己一个人住 你也不会脱光光到处走啊
Why does it takes me so long to answer the door?
你以为我为何老半天才应门？
So far,is this trip to Las Vegas better or worse than the trip to London?
这趟旅程旅程到现在为止 比起伦敦那趟好还是坏？
So far, it's pretty much the same,Phoebe.
菲比，到现在为止都差不多
What about after I give you these candies?
好，那我给你们糖果之后呢？
I guess it's a little better now.
对，我想好一点了
Las Vegas,1. London,0.
好，赌城1分，伦敦0分
I'll be back.
我马上回来
Happy Plane-aversary.
飞机纪念日快乐
I love you.
我爱你
-Can I give you your present now? -Okay!
礼物能趁现在给你吗？ 好啊
Oh, don't tell me I did this.
要命，不会吧？
I love "l forgot the present" fake-out!
我最爱你假装没带礼物了
How about "I did forget the present, forgive me" not fake-out?
那如果我是真的没带礼物 请你多多包涵呢？
You can give it to me when we get back.
没关系啦，别放在心上 等回去再给我就行了
This is the worst thing that could happen.
纪念日发生这种事 真是再扫兴不过了
You decided to tell him about the Richard thing.
很好，你最后还是决定 要跟钱德说理查的事了
What "Richard thing"?
什么理查的事？
Oh,no.
糟糕
What "Richard thing"?
什么理查的事？
Simmons. Go with Simmons.
用西蒙斯混过去
I ran into Richard yesterday.
好吧，我昨天遇到了理查
He asked me if I wanted to go for a bite and I did.
他问我要不要一起吃饭 我答应了
I didn't tell you because you'd get mad...
我没跟你说是因为我知道你会生气
...and I didn't wanna spoil our anniversary.
而我不想毁了周年纪念日
I'm not mad.
我不生气啊
Really?
真的？ 是啊…
So you bumped into Richard. You grabbed a "bite."
你遇到理查，一起吃饭
No big deal.
没啥大不了的
Great.
太好了
Okay, London,1.
好，伦敦1分
This is gonna be a real horserace.
这将会是一场拉锯战
Oh,look what happened.
怎么会这样
Check me out.
瞧瞧我自己
I'm in my kitchen...
我在自家的厨房
...naked.
脱光光
I'm picking up an orange.
拿起一颗柳丁
I'm naked.
我脱光光
I'm lighting the candles.
点起蜡烛
Naked. And carefully.
脱光光，要小心
Oh,my God! That's Rachel, naked!
天啊，瑞秋脱光光
I can't look at that. I am looking at this.
不能看，我在看书
Okay, vivid colors, expressive brush strokes.
好，鲜明的色彩、有力的笔触
Unless she wants me to be looking at that.
她故意要我看就另当别论了
She knows I'm home.
她知道我在家
She knows I can see her.
她知道我看得到她
What kind of game is she playing?
她这是在玩什么把戏？
I think maybe someone's lonely tonight.
也许今晚有人寂寞
Dr. Geller.
盖勒博士
Stop it. You're being silly.
别胡思乱想 自讨没趣了
Or am I?
真是这样吗？
Love to love you baby
Damn it!
讨厌
May I come in?
我可以进去吗？
Yeah,if you want to.
想要的话就进来啊
Do you want me to?
你要我进去吗？
Yeah,sure?
当然罗？
So do l.
彼此彼此
Okay,Rach,before anything happens...
瑞秋，在一切还没开始之前
...I wanna lay down a couple of ground rules.
有几个原则我想先说清楚
This is just about tonight.
这只适用于今晚
I won't go through with this if it'll raise the question of "us."
今晚过后，你是你，我是我
I just want this to be...
好吗？我希望这一切…
...about what it is.
只是各取所需
And...
...what is that,Ross?
罗斯，什么各取所需？
The physical act of love.
出自于兽欲的性爱
What, are you crazy?
什么？你疯了不成？
So you weren't trying to entice me just now with your nakedness?
所以你刚才脱光光 不是在勾引我？
Oh,God. You saw me?
天啊，你有看到？
You weren't trying to entice me with your nakedness?
你脱光光不是在勾引我
You actually thought I wanted to have sex with you?
当然不是 你当真以为我想跟你上床？
才不是呢…
不是
不是…
Oh,wow. I'm sorry. But,Ross, you kicked off your shoes.
我很抱歉 可是你还把鞋踢掉了耶
-Can we just forget this ever happened? -Of course. You're right. I'm sorry.
能不能忘了这件事？ 当然可以，没问题 你说的对，抱歉
-Thank you. -Yes.
谢谢
-I guess I'm gonna go pack. -Okay. Wait,one more thing.
那我应该回去打包了 好 等等，还有一件事
Do we still need to settle the question of "us"?
还要解决谁是谁的问题吗？
Hey,you guys,wait! You guys.
你们等等啊
This place is much better than London.
等等我 这地方比伦敦好多了吧
A lady dressed like Cleopatra gave me this.
有个打扮成埃及艳后的女士 给了我这张折价券
Ninety-nine cent steak and lobster dinner.
99美分就能吃到牛排龙虾晚餐
You don't eat animals.
菲比，你又不吃肉
For ninety-nine cents I'd eat you.
不用一美元，我连你都吃
I can totally settle down here.
我完全可以耗在这里
It's got everything I could ever want. Including Joey! Look!
我要的东西应有尽有 就连乔伊都在，你们看！
Look! Hey!
快点看！
Oh,my God.
天啊
乔伊！
Love your condoms,my man.
你的保险套真不赖
Why are you here? I told you not to come.
你们怎么在这里？ 不是要你们别来了？
Why are you dressed as a gladiator?
你干嘛打扮成神鬼战士？
Because I'm shooting a scene right now. I play a gladiator.
因为我正在拍戏 我扮演神鬼战士
Hold on a second. Can we cut?
你们等等 可以卡一下吗？
My friends are here. I'm gonna take a break.
我朋友来了 我要休息一下
Who are you talking to?
你是在跟谁说话？
The director.
导演啊
Her.
就是她
All right,it's not a gladiator movie. I work here.
好啦，我不是在拍神鬼战士 我在这里工作
Why? What happened?
为什么？发生了什么事？
The movie shut down. Ran out of money.
那部电影因为没钱而停拍
I'm working here till it starts up, if it ever does.
我在这里工作等电影重新开拍 如果真有这一天的话
-I'm so sorry. -Such a drag.
我真的很遗撼
Sorry I didn't tell you. I'm sorry.
对不起 没跟你们说，抱歉
Apparently there's a new policy of not sharing.
没关系… 互相隐瞒显然成了新的规矩
-I knew you weren't okay with that. -So you're a gladiator!
我就知道你听了会有疙瘩 你是神鬼战士耶
What's going on?
他们怎么了？
-Monica had lunch with Richard. -Dawson?
摩妮卡跟理查吃了中饭 理查道森？（英国演员）
But that would've been so cool!
不是啦，要不然一定超酷的
Her boyfriend Richard.
是那个男朋友理查
It meant nothing. After all this time, how can you not trust me?
那根本不碍事 你怎么到现在还不相信我？
When you go lunching with hunky men and don't tell me!
你瞒着我跟大胡子帅哥吃午餐 要我怎么相信你？
You're right. I'm sorry. I should've told you.
你说的对，对不起 我早该跟你说的
Thanks.
谢谢
-There we go. -Now I love Vegas.
这样才对嘛 我爱赌城
I promise you next time I absolutely will tell you.
我保证下次一定会跟你说
-"Next time"? -So close.
下一次？ 败在最后
There won't be a next time. You cannot see him again.
下不为例，你不能再跟他见面
I cannot see him? You can't tell me what to do.
我不能跟他见面？ 你不能对我发号施令
That's funny, I think I just did.
有趣，刚才不就是了
If you act like this, I won't be around you.
你这种态度，我眼不见为净 我无所谓
-Fine. -Happy anniversary!
好！纪念日快乐
Guys,please! Come on,come on.
你们别这样嘛
This is obviously a misunderstanding.
这显然是个大误会
No,it is not.
才不是误会 你在说什么…
Don't look at me. I just work here.
别看我，我只是在这里工作
Okay, Ross? I'm a little warm, so I'm gonna be taking off my sweater.
罗斯，我有点热，要脱毛衣
Now,I'm just letting you know...
我只是要你知道
...this is not an invitation to the physical act of love.
这不是在勾引你一夜情
Yep,that's hilarious.
对，真是太爆笑了
I'm sorry. I'm done. I'm done.
抱歉，我不闹了…
You know,last night was embarrassing for you too.
昨晚对你其实也很尴尬
No,not really. You've seen me naked hundreds of times.
不尽然啦 你看过我裸体几百次了
But it was a first for the rest of my building.
但对我其他楼友是第一次 好吧
That's true. But I just don't embarrass that easily.
话是这样说没错啦 但我没有那么容易尴尬
What? You totally get embarrassed.
什么？你根本尴尬得要死
No,I don't. Ross,I think I'm just a more secure person than you are.
才没有 这是因为我比你更有安全感
-ls that so? -Yeah.
是吗？ 是啊
Hey,lady!
小姐
I don't care how much you want it,okay?
不管你有多想
I am not gonna have sex with you in the bathroom!
我绝不会和你去厕所做爱
You know,in Roman times, this was more than just a hat.
在古罗马时代 这不只是顶帽子而已
-Really? -Yeah,sure,sure.
是吗？ 当然罗…
They would scrub the floors.
这可以用来刷地板
They'd use it to get the mud off their shoe.
抹去鞋子上的泥巴
Sometimes underneath the horse would get dirty.
有时候马腹会弄脏
So they would stick it right
把这个戮进去就能...
I can't believe this is how I'm spending my anniversary.
乔伊，真不敢相信 我的周年纪念日是这样过的
I'll take you someplace nice. A guy tipped me $100.
但我带你去个好地方 今天有个人给我一百美元小费
He was playing blackjack for an hour and he won $5000.
他玩21点 才一小时就赢了五千美元
Can you believe that?
你相信吗？五千美元耶！
If I won $5000,I'd join a gym.
若我赢了五千美元 我就去加入健身房
Build up my upper body...
把我的上半身练壮
...and hit Richard from behind with a stick.
再用棍子插理查的屁眼
Wait! Why don't I just do what that guy did?
等等，我何不效法那个人？
I'll take this $100, turn it into $5000...
把这一百元变成五千
...and I'll turn that into enough to get my movie going!
到时再连三翻 就有钱让电影重新开拍了
Good luck.
祝你好运了
I don't need luck. I've thought this through.
钱德，我不需要好运 我已经想透了
I see.
我懂了
Thanks.
谢谢你 多谢
I can't believe this. This is like the worst night ever.
不敢相信，今晚真是糟透了
You had a minor setback in your relationship.
摩妮卡，你和钱德的关系 有了小小挫折
Big deal. It's only Chandler.
有啥大不了？不过是钱德罢了
I am so sorry.
我真的很遗撼
This is crazy. Such a stupid argument....
我们吵架的理由太蠢了
I don't wanna see Richard.
我根本不想跟理查再见面
So go fix it.
那就去挽回啊
Find Chandler. He's probably in your room.
去找钱德 他八成就待在你房间里
Tell him sorry and you love him.
跟他说对不起，说你爱他
You're right,Phoebe.
菲比，你说的对
-Thank you. -Sure.
谢谢你 小意思
Yeah! Las Vegas! Number one!
好耶，叫赌城第一名！
Anybody lose this?
这是谁掉的吗？
Coming out. Place your bet.
下注吧
Dice her out.
下好离手
Yellow 11. Pay the front line!
一赔二，不还本
So I'm on my way back to the bathroom.
我正好要去厕所
All right, all right. Just keep walking, all right?
好啦…继续走就是了
What are you? I am sorry,sir.
罗斯，你干嘛… 先生，对不起
I think he just really likes you.
他太喜欢你了
You know that teacher who had a baby with her student?
你知道那个老师吗？ 跟学生生孩子的那个？
搞什么…
-Can I help you? -Yes.
嗨 小姐，需要我效劳吗？对
Do you have any extra pants? My friend seems to have had a little accident.
不好意思 你们有多的裤子吗？ 我朋友出了点小状况
-Can I change $100? -Changing $100.
可以换一百元筹码吗？ 换一百元筹码
-Good luck, sir. -Thanks.
先生，祝您好运
That's right.
全押了
-Thirteen. -Hit me!
13点 再来
Oh,man!
要命！
Wait!
慢着！
You are not gonna believe this!
钱德，说了你一定不相信
I have found my identical hand twin.
我找到我的双胞手了！
What?
什么？
My identical hand twin!
我的双胞手啊！
What's an identical hand twin?
什么是双胞手？
What does it sound like?
听起来像什么？
It's a guy with my identical hands.
有个人的手跟我一模一样
It was incredible. The dealer's hands were exactly like mine.
钱德，太不可思议了 发牌员的手跟我一模一样
It was like looking at my hands in a mirror!
就跟照镜子没两样
You sure you weren't looking at your hands in a mirror?
你确定不是在照镜子？
Don't you see what this means? I can forget about that stupid movie.
你不懂这件事的意义吗？ 我大可忘了那部蠢电影
I'm gonna be a millionaire!
我要变成百万富翁了！
-How? -I don't have it all worked out yet.
怎么变？ 我还没有完全想出来
But it's gotta mean big money. Come on, identical hands!
不过保证很有赚头 拜托，一模一样的手耶！
Again,I must go back to...
我得再问一次
...how?
怎么赚？
This is Vegas,man. People will pay to see freaky stuff!
这里可是赌城 大家就爱付钱看怪东西
How much would you pay to see this hand...
好，你愿意付多少钱 看这只手
...twice?
两次？
I can't really put a price on that.
乔伊，我说不太出个价钱
Are you un-supporting me again?
你又不支持我了？
I support you 100%. I just didn't get it right away.
不…我百分之百支持你 只是我一时没回过神来
Now I'm caught up.
我现在懂了
Identical hand twins.
双胞手！
It's a million-dollar idea!
这点子值上一百万
Right? I know. Okay. All right.
我知道…
What's that for?
那是干嘛的？
Well,I gotta document this before that dealer gets off his break.
照相存证，免得发牌员落跑
I found my identical hand twin!
我找到我的双胞手了！
Oh,you're so lucky!
你真幸运
So where's Monica? Did you guys make up?
摩妮卡呢？你们和好没？
But she just came up here.
没有啊 可是她刚才上来了啊
That was Joey.
那是乔伊
I wonder where she is? It's so weird.
怪了，那她去了哪里？
She's probably talking to Richard.
或许在跟理查说话吧
Would you stop that?
你有完没完？
You know what she said after her lunch with Richard?
你知道他和理查吃完中饭 回来后第一句话是什么吗？
She didn't feel anything for him. She loves you.
她对他完全没感觉了 她爱的是你
-Really? -Yes.
真的？ 对
She feels terrible. She really wants to make up. You've gotta find her.
而且她很难过 她真的很想跟你和好 你一定得找到她
Good.
好
I should really start wearing hats.
我真应该开始戴帽子
我的色子呢？
Welcome to Las Vegas.
欢迎来到赌城
-Did you enjoy your flight? -I did.
一路还愉快吗？ 对
Thank you very much. It was excellent.
谢谢，非常棒
-I hope you had a nice flight. -Oh,it was the best.
希望您一路还愉快 太愉快了
I think the check-in is that way.
登记柜台应该在那里
Kids love me.
小孩子最喜欢我了
Hi,you guys are here!
菲比 你们来了！
What'd you do? Did you go to a costume party?
嗨 你去参加化妆舞会了？
Let me guess. Pancho Villa.
我来猜，你是扮庞丘维亚（墨西哥革命英雄）？
And you're Bob Saget.
你是鲍伯塞吉（演员）
Pancho Villa?
庞丘维亚？ 是啊
What are you talking about,Phoebe? I don't
菲比，你在说什么啊？ 我不…
Oh,my God! You drew on me?
天啊，你偷画我？
Hey,you wet my pants!
谁叫你弄湿我裤子！
What kind of party was this?
这是哪种派对啊？
I've been walking around like this? You have so crossed a line.
我打从下飞机就是这样子 你实在是太过份了
Rach,wait. The men's room is that way.
瑞秋，等等，男厕在那里
It's the third time she's won on a machine I was playing.
怎么了？ 那女士接我手玩，结果赢钱 这已经是第三次了
I bet she's one of those people.
我赌她一定是那种人
Mole people?
间谍？
What? No, a lurker.
不是啦，是跟赌人
What's that?
跟赌人是什么？
When you're playing a machine and it hasn't paid out...
你玩赌博机，没有赢钱
...a lurker waits for you to give up and then
跟赌人等你放弃就来接手玩 然后…
Kills you?
杀你灭口？
They swoop in and steal your jackpot.
不是啦，他们半路杀进来 偷走本来你会中的大奖
-How do you know about this? -My nana used to do it.
你怎么会知道这种事 我褓姆以前就干这行
That's how she paid for my dance Karate lessons.
她就是用这收入 帮我付舞蹈…空手道的学费
Dance karate?
舞蹈空手道？
Yes,it's a deadly...
对，那是种...
...but beautiful sport.
...美丽却致命的运动
-lt won't come off. -What?
我弄不掉 什么？
It won't come off.
我弄不掉
Oh,my God. Rach, are you sure?
天啊，瑞秋，你确定吗？
I took it off and then I drew it back on.
不确定，其实我弄掉了 又自己再画回去
Rach,I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm sure we can get it off,okay?
我真的很抱歉 我确定一定可以弄掉的
-Just give me your pen. -Why? What are you gonna do?
把你的笔给我 干嘛？做什么用？
Well,I believe I'm going to stab you repeatedly.
我要让你万笔穿心
Not here. There are cameras everywhere.
别在这里 到处都有监视摄影机
You made it!
你们到了！
乔伊
Who's your friend? He's hot.
你朋友是谁？他真辣
Thanks,man.
多谢夸奖
Listen,I talked to Chandler. And I'm sorry about the movie.
钱德跟我说过了 电影的事我很遗撼
Don't be sorry.
不用抱歉
I don't need it anymore. I found my identical hand twin.
不要也罢 我找到我的双胞手
Your what?
你的什么？
My identical hand twin. The person whose hands are like mine.
我的双胞手 那个人的手掌跟我完全一样
-Were you looking for this person? -Not even. This thing is a gold mine.
你特别去找的？ 正好撞见的，这可是金矿
What?
什么？
That won't make you any money.
靠那个赚不了钱的
Well,fine.
好，你这样想也无所谓
None of you will live with me in my hand-shaped mansion.
到时我盖了手掌形的大厦 你们谁都休想来住
Except you. You can live in the thumb.
菲比，你例外，大拇指给你住
All right,baby,come on!
好吧，加油！
I am on fire!
漂亮！挡都挡不住！
See you later.
摩妮卡，再见
What are you doing?
等等，钱德，你在干嘛？
What's it look like? Going home.
你看呢？我要回家
Why?
等等，为什么？
Wait. Sorry,I was just playing for one second.
你等等 对不起，我只是下来玩一下
If you don't want me to see Richard again,I won't.
我本来打算要跟你说 若你不让我理查再见面 我答应
He means nothing to me.
他对我没有任何意义
Oh,come on. I was there.
得了吧，我又不是瞎子
I know he's the love of your life.
我知道他是你追求的真爱
Not anymore.
现在不是了
Really?
真的？
Really.
真的
All right?
Let's forget about going home and celebrate our anniversary.
忘了什么要回家的事 我们来庆祝周年纪念日
Okay, this is empty.
袋子里是空的
I wanted to make a dramatic scene, but I hate packing.
我想要搞得很戏剧化 可是我又讨厌打包
Where's the other guy?
另一个人呢？
Which guy?
哪个人？
Tall,dark hair,hand looks exactly like this?
高高的，深色头发 手掌跟我一模一样，你看
I don't know about the hands, but he went to the restroom.
我不知道什么手掌的 不过在我之前的发牌员 刚去上厕所了
好
How you doing?
你好吗？
-Very busy. -Right. Okay.
我很忙 对耶！好吧
Yes,hello. I have a question.
你好，我有个问题
I used your pen to draw on my friend's face.
我用你们的笔，画我朋友的脸
A beard and a mustache.
画了胡子
Thank you.
谢谢你
No,she didn't think so.
不，她不以为然
I know. It's like Anyway....
对啊，那其实…
Makeup didn't cover it, we've tried everything and nothing's worked.
用化妆品盖不过去 我们试过所有方法都去不掉
What do we do?
这要怎么办？
对，是…
Thank you.
好…多谢
Yeah, it's not coming off.
对，这个墨水擦不掉
What? What else did he say?
什么？那他还说了什么？
He said he thought I was funny.
他说他觉得我很逗
Okay, look. Let's just go downstairs...
好，你听我说… 我们下楼去...
...we'll have some fun and you will forget all about it.
好好玩玩 你就会忘记这回事了
There's no way I am leaving looking like this!
休想，罗斯，我顶着这个样子 绝对不出房门
Come on,Rach. It's not that bad.
别这样啦，没有那么难看
Ross,I am a human doodle!
罗斯，我变成人体涂鸦了！
Just because some idiot drew on your face doesn't mean you can't have fun.
别因为一个白痴在你脸上乱画 而阻碍你玩乐的权利
Besides,no one will even look at you.
而且又没人会看你
This is Vegas. Hello? There are tons of other freaks here.
这里可是赌城，怪人一大堆
There are tons of freaks here. No other. No.
这里有一大堆怪人，你不算
Come on. No one will notice. I swear.
走啦，我发誓没人会注意到
There was some staring and pointing.
好啦，是有一些人指指点点
I need a drink.
我得喝点酒
They really overcharge you for that stuff.
冰箱里的酒都太贵了
But who cares, because it's all on me.
但是谁在乎呢？我请客
That is one big drink.
你的一点酒还真不少
Macadamia nut?
要吃夏威夷果仁吗？
Wow! That's some pricey nut.
这个果仁还真值钱
Really like those macadamia nuts?
你真的很喜欢吃果仁呢
Nope.
不喜欢
Get out of here, you lurker!
跟赌人，走开啦
Go on,get!
滚啦
You made up.
你们和好了
I couldn't be mad at him for too long.
是啊，我没办法一直生他的气
She couldn't live without the "Chand love."
没有钱德的爱，她就不能活
Get a room.
去开房间啦
-We have one. -Use it.
我们有房间 我知道，快去用啊
Bye,Chandler. Bye,Mon.
钱德，摩妮卡，再见
Phoebe,Phoebe. Please pick up a house phone.
菲比…请至店内接电话
You have a call from Chandler and Mon.
钱德和摩妮卡有事找
Hello,Chandler and Mon. Hello?
喂？钱德、摩妮卡，喂？…
You dirty lurker!
你这个死跟赌人
I'm sorry,you are the same old lady,right? Yeah. Dirty lurker!
抱歉，你就是那位老太太吧？ 死跟赌人！
That's right. Take good care of those babies.
可得好好照顾你的手
Excuse me?
你说什么？
It's me. Joey.
我是乔伊啊
Do I know you?
我认识你吗？
Joey?
乔伊啊
Yeah, the hand guy.
秀手的那个
So, what are we gonna do about this hand twin thing?
我们要怎么处理双胞手的事？
Nothing.
不用处理？
Look,you and I have been given a gift.
你和我拥有上帝的赐礼
We have to do something with it. Like hand modeling. Or magic.
我们得要好好利用 好比手部模特儿或是变魔术
And you know NASA's gonna want to talk to us.
太空总署一定也想找我们聊聊
I have to get back to work.
我得回去工作了… 等等…
We can have our own show.
我们可以自己组秀
We can clap our hands together. People will love it!
我们把手掌合在一起 大家一定超爱看的
And I wrote a song for us.
我还替我们写了一首主题曲
This hand is your hand
这是你的手
This hand is my hand
这是我的手
Oh,wait,that's your hand
等等，那是你的手才对
No,wait,it's my hand
不对，是我的手才对
-That's okay. -But you haven't even heard the chorus!
还是算了 你还没听到副歌啊
Oh,my God.
天啊
I look like my great-aunt Muriel.
我现在看起来 就像我姑婆茉莉儿
All right,you know what?
We don't have to go downstairs.
其实我们用不着下楼
We can bring Vegas up to us.
房间里就可以是赌城
All right,come on.
快
We'll play some blackjack. Here we go.
我们来玩21点 来罗
-Thirteen. -Hit me.
13点 再加
Twenty-three.
23，爆了
Which is what we play to at this casino!
我们这里23点最大
You win 10 dollars!
你赢了10美元
-I bet 20. -Right.
我押了20美元 没错
A new pair of shoes for the Chan-Chan man!
帮我的小钱钱买双新鞋
I've never seen a roll like this!
我这辈子还没看过有这么旺的
That's right, baby!
宝贝，你说对了
What do I want now?
这次要押几号？
Eight?
好，8号？
-Six. -Pick a number! That is your only job.
还是6号？ 选一个啦！你只有这个任务！
-Eight. -Thank you.
8号… 8号
If you get this, we buy everybody a steak dinner.
如果你中了这一把 晚餐就请在场的各位吃牛排
Eight it is.
8号
We're not buying steak dinners,are we?
我们真的要请他们吃牛排？
-No. -Okay,good.
假的 那就好
-What do I want now? -Try a hard eight.
这次要押几号？ 再硬押个8
-What? -Two fours.
什么？4加4啦
Eight!
8号
Don't you let her go. You're a lucky guy.
千万要把握住她，你太幸运了
Thank you,Mr. Drunken Gambler.
谢谢你，醉赌徒先生
You get this and we get the biggest suite in the place.
好，如果你中了这一把 我们就租下这里最大的套房
We get the biggest suite in the place.
等等…我说的是我和她租下这里最大的套房
The biggest suite in the place!
好，这里最大的套房来罗
Come on!
I love you! I can't remember why we fought.
我爱你 我都忘记我们在吵什么了
Because I had lunch with Rich
因为我和理查吃中饭…
Me neither!
我也忘了！
-What now? -Another hard eight.
这次要押几号？ 再硬押一次8
Hard eight? Let's call it easy eight!
硬押8？简单8才对
I'll tell you what. You roll another hard eight...
好，这样吧，如果这次再中…
...and we get married here tonight.
我们今晚就在这里结婚
快啊…
Shut up!
闭嘴！
It just got interesting!
好戏才正要上场！
What did you say?
你刚才说什么？
You roll another hard eight, we get married tonight.
你再赢一次8 我们今晚就在这里结婚
You serious?
你是认真的？
Yes. I love you.
是啊，我爱你
I've never loved anybody as much as I love you.
我不曾这样爱过一个人
我也不曾这样爱过一个人
So if an eight comes up, we take it as a sign and we do it.
好，如果再出8就是天意 我们赶今晚结婚
What do you say?
好不好？
Okay.
好
来吧…
That's a four.
有一个是4
-And where's the other one? -Under the table.
另一个呢？ 掉到桌子底下了
Nobody move! You look that way,I look this way.
通通不许动！ 你找那边，我找这边 好！
Here it is,here it is.
在这里…
That could be 4 or 5.
一半4，一半5
It's your call.
你决定
It's a four.
那是4
I think so too.
我也这样觉得
Oh, well, lost again.
好吧，又没赢到钱
That's it. You and me. Outside!
够了，我们去外面解决
I wouldn't want you to lose a chunk of that pretty blond hair!
我可不想看到 你美丽的金发少了一撮
Be cool.
假装没事…
Okay, your lurking days are over.
女士，你跟赌的日子结束了
What?
什么？
Everyone you lurk, I'll lurk first.
从现在开始 我要抢先你一步
You move on, I'll be one step ahead of you...
不管你找谁下手 我都会捷足先登
...every single time.
一次都不放过
And then I'll be on your ass every hour of every day...
我每天都会紧紧跟着你…
...till Monday...
直到星期一
...because that's when I go home.
因为我那天要回家
When do you leave?
你何时要回家？
Also Monday.
也是星期一
What time? Maybe we can share a cab.
几点？说不定能共乘计程车
Hit me.
再加
We need more cards.
我们得再去买牌
Yeah. And we also need more drinks. Hold on a second.
对，还要再来点酒，你等等
好了
Hello,Vegas?
赌城吗？
We would like more alcohol.
我们还需要酒
You know what else? We would like some more beers.
对了，再来点啤酒
Oh,I forgot to dial.
我竟然忘了拨号
That must be our alcohol and beers.
一定是送酒来了
It's Joey! I love Joey!
是乔伊！我爱乔伊
Oh,I love Joey!
我爱乔伊
Joey lives with a duck.
乔伊跟鸭子住一起
嗨
Look,I need some help, okay?
你们听我说，我需要帮助
Someone has to convince my hand twin to cooperate.
谁去叫我那双胞手合作点
I'll do it. Whatever you need me to do, I'm your man.
我去 不管你有什么需要 找我就对了
Are you okay?
你还好吧？
Yeah. Fine. Thanks.
对，我很好，谢了
Hey, Rach?
瑞秋
How you doing?
你好吗？
I'm doing good, baby. How you doing?
宝贝，我很好，你呢？
Don't let her drink anymore.
罗斯，别再让她喝了
Here's that macadamia nut.
是那颗夏威夷果仁
No,something else.
不对，是别的东西
So, what do you wanna do now?
好吧，你现在要干嘛？
I wanna get out of the room.
我要离开这房间
I really miss downstairs.
我真想念楼下
Okay,you know what? There is only one way I am leaving this hotel room.
我跟你说，要我离开这间房 只有一个方法
Well,hello!
嗨
I'm Ross.
我是罗斯
-Good luck to you. -Sir, you've got a little something....
祝你好运 抱歉，先生，你脸上有东西
Hello.
你好 你好
你好
I won!
我赢了！
I won! I finally won!
我赢了！我终于赢了
I won! That was my quarter!
是我赢才对，那是我的硬币
Take a hike, toots.
好啦，还给你，滚吧
Excuse me, sir.
先生，不好意思
This lady played my quarter. This is my money.
这位小姐用我的硬币玩 这是我赢的钱
Is that true, miss?
小姐，真的是这样吗？
Sells drugs to kids.
卖毒品给小孩
什么？
She sells drugs to kids.
她卖毒品给小孩
It was my quarter.
那是我的硬币
Was it her quarter?
那硬币是她的吗？
How about we talk about this over dinner?
我们等吃晚餐再聊如何？
-Okay, lady, you're out of here. -No,you can't arrest me!
好了，小姐，请你出去 不！…你不能逮捕我
I won't go back to that hellhole!
我才不要重回火坑！
I'm just taking you outside.
我只是要把你带出去而已
那好吧
I need something old, something new, something borrowed and something blue.
快点，一定要凑齐四样东西 我们才能结婚
Here's something blue and new.
这是蓝色的，而且也是新的
You are so efficient. I love you.
我们真有效率，我爱你
-Let's go. -No,wait!
走吧 还不行…
We need something old.
我们还需要旧的东西
I have a condom in my wallet that I've had since I was twelve.
好，我皮夹里有个保险套 我从12岁放到现在
That'll work.
那符合啊（亦指“还能用”）
I don't think so.
我想应该不能用了
Now something borrowed.
好，现在只剩借来的东西
Here, just take this.
那就把这毛衣拿走
That's stealing.
这是偷窃耶
We'll bring it back. Put it under your dress.
到时再还回来就是了 塞进你的洋装里
Okay. One thing at a time.
好啦，先结婚再怀孕
-Are you gonna play? -No,I don't really have any money.
你要玩吗？ 不要，我没半毛钱
Not yet,anyway.
只是时候未到而已
Can't sit here if you don't play.
你不玩就不能坐在这里
My name is Regina Falangie.
嗨，我是瑞吉娜佛兰姬
I'm a businesswoman in town on business.
我是生意人，这趟是来出差的
Would you like to see my card?
你要我的名片吗？
What did I do with my Filofax?
我的名片夹到哪儿去了？
I must've left it in Conference Room B.
一定是忘在B会议室
-Fourteen. -Hit me.
14点 再加
Oh,my God.
天啊
May I just say that you two gentlemen have the exact same hands?
两位的手一模一样
They're identical.
一个模子刻出来的
I've never seen that in the business world.
我在商业界做了这么久 从来没看过这种事
Stop it.
别再说了
Miss Falangie,may I ask you a question as an impartial person at this table?
佛兰姬女士，以局外人的身份 我能请教你一个问题吗？
Please stop it.
请你别再说了
Wouldn't you pay good money to see identical hands...
你愿不愿意花大钱 去看手长一模一样的两个人…
...showcased in some type of an entertainment venue?
这种娱乐性的演出？
If you leave now,I will chop off my hand and give it to you!
只要你愿意离开 我就把手砍下来送你！
Didn't I just throw you out?
我不是才把你赶出去了吗？
No, you threw out Phoebe.
不，你赶出去的是菲比
I'm Regina Falangie. Falangie.
我是瑞吉娜佛兰姬女士
Come on, lady.
小姐，你别闹了
Please take him too.
请你把他也带走
Me? Oh, come on, man.
我？别这样嘛
Come on, buddy.
走吧…
Don't let him do this. Come on!
你不能这样
I'm your hand twin!
我是你的双胞手耶
Hello. One marriage,please.
嗨，登记结婚
We want to get married.
对，我们要结婚
There's a service in progress. Have a seat.
有婚礼正在进行，先请坐
All right.
好吧…
What are you doing?
你在干嘛？
The "Wedding March." Does that freak you out?
那是结婚进行曲 听了有没有吓到？
No, it's the graduation song.
没有，因为那是毕业歌
This is it. We're gonna get married.
好，来吧 我们要结婚了
You sure you wanna do this?
你确定你真的想结婚？
Hello, Mrs. Ross!
嗨，罗斯太太
Well,hello, Mr. Rachel!
嗨，瑞秋先生
Wait. Okay.
等等，好